const questions = [
    {
        question: "Old Lyme Connecticut has a museum dedicated to?",
        options: ["nuts", "berries", "butterflies"],
        correctAnswer: "butterflies"
    },
    {
        question: "Who composed the opera Il Travatore (Трубадур)?",
        options: ["W. A. Mozart", "G. Verdi", "P.I. Tchaikovsky"],
        correctAnswer: "G. Verdi"
    },
    {
        question: "If you have cherophobia what are you afraid of?",
        options: ["cabin fever", "sadness", "happiness"],
        correctAnswer: "happiness"
    },
    {
        question: "What financial item was introduced to UK in September 1963?",
        options: ["Guardian", "Financial Times", "American Express"],
        correctAnswer: "Financial Times"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country in the world produces the most mangos?",
        options: ["India", "Israel", "Australia"],
        correctAnswer: "India"
    },
    {
        question: "What was Helen Keller's first word (Miracle worker)?",
        options: ["mom", "water", "teacher"],
        correctAnswer: "water"
    },
    {
        question: "What do the Germans now celebrate on October 3rd?",
        options: ["Unity Day", "independence Day", "Gratitude Day"],
        correctAnswer: "Unity Day"
    },
    {
        question: "In 1900 caterer Harry Stevens introduced what words to language?",
        options: ["Coca-Cola", "Hot Dogs", "Adidas"],
        correctAnswer: "Hot Dogs"
    },
    {
        question: "In Saudi Arabia by law women may not become what?",
        options: ["a teacher", "an engineer", "a doctor"],
        correctAnswer: "a teacher"
    },
    {
        question: "In Bavaria what is defined as a staple food?",
        options: ["beer", "water", "sauerkraut"],
        correctAnswer: "beer"
    },
    {
        question: "“Reject” means?",
        options: ["turn back", "turn in", "turn down"],
        correctAnswer: "turn down"
    },
    {
        question: "What lexical unit doesn’t belong to the Italian language?",
        options: ["felicita", "oronero", "navidad"],
        correctAnswer: "navidad"
    },
    {
        question: "Vor was the Norse Goddess of what?",
        options: ["Truth", "Love", "Indignity"],
        correctAnswer: "Love"
    },
    {
        question: "What fashion designer was responsible for 'The New Look'?",
        options: ["Versace", "Christian Dior", "Chanel"],
        correctAnswer: "Christian Dior"
    },
    {
        question: "Marie Tussaud was born in what country?",
        options: ["Switzerland", "Italy", "France"],
        correctAnswer: "France"
    }
];
